{
    "subject": "Toán 6",
    "topic": "PHÉP CỘNG VÀ TRỪ HAI SỐ NGUYÊN",
    "questions": 
  [
  { "id": "fill61", "type": "fill", "question": "Câu 61. Tính: -(-48 - 35) + (-27 + 14) = ?", "correctAnswer": "70" },
  { "id": "fill62", "type": "fill", "question": "Câu 62. Tính: (56 - (-33)) - (-42 + 19) = ?", "correctAnswer": "112" },
  { "id": "fill63", "type": "fill", "question": "Câu 63. Tính: -((27 - 49) - (-38)) + 16 = ?", "correctAnswer": "0" },
  { "id": "fill64", "type": "fill", "question": "Câu 64. Tính: ((-25) + 64) - (48 - (-19)) = ?", "correctAnswer": "-28" },
  { "id": "fill65", "type": "fill", "question": "Câu 65. Tính: -(-72 + (-14)) - (36 + (-20)) = ?", "correctAnswer": "70" },
  { "id": "fill66", "type": "fill", "question": "Câu 66. Tính: (83 - (−27)) - (−45 − 32) = ?", "correctAnswer": "187" },
  { "id": "fill67", "type": "fill", "question": "Câu 67. Tính: -((−18) − (−46)) + (27 − (−15)) = ?", "correctAnswer": "14" },
  { "id": "fill68", "type": "fill", "question": "Câu 68. Tính: ((-35) - (-62)) - ((-48) + 19) = ?", "correctAnswer": "56" },
  { "id": "fill69", "type": "fill", "question": "Câu 69. Tính: -((-44) + (-33)) + (-15 - (-28)) = ?", "correctAnswer": "90" },
  { "id": "fill70", "type": "fill", "question": "Câu 70. Tính: (−81 + 56) − (−39 − 22) = ?", "correctAnswer": "36" },
  { "id": "fill71", "type": "fill", "question": "Câu 71. Tính: -((64 - (−29)) + (-17)) + 48 = ?", "correctAnswer": "-28" },
  { "id": "fill72", "type": "fill", "question": "Câu 72. Tính: ((-59) − (−46)) − ((-33) − (−12)) = ?", "correctAnswer": "8" },
  { "id": "fill73", "type": "fill", "question": "Câu 73. Tính: -((-25 - (-47)) - (−36 + 14)) = ?", "correctAnswer": "-44" },
  { "id": "fill74", "type": "fill", "question": "Câu 74. Tính: ((28 + (−45)) − (−53)) + (−12) = ?", "correctAnswer": "24" },
  { "id": "fill75", "type": "fill", "question": "Câu 75. Tính: −((−36 + 27) + (48 − 59)) − 21 = ?", "correctAnswer": "-1" },
  { "id": "fill76", "type": "fill", "question": "Câu 76. Tính: (−92 − (−18)) − ((−35) + 47) = ?", "correctAnswer": "-86" },
  { "id": "fill77", "type": "fill", "question": "Câu 77. Tính: ((73 − (−41)) − (−52 − 13)) = ?", "correctAnswer": "179" },
  { "id": "fill78", "type": "fill", "question": "Câu 78. Tính: −((−58) − (−26)) + ((-19) + 44) = ?", "correctAnswer": "57" },
  { "id": "fill79", "type": "fill", "question": "Câu 79. Tính: ((-17) - (−43)) − (−28 + (−19)) = ?", "correctAnswer": "73" },
  { "id": "fill80", "type": "fill", "question": "Câu 80. Tính: −((-64 + 29) − (−41 − 37)) = ?", "correctAnswer": "-43" }
]
  }